cdicollege.ca 2019-07-18

# CDI College | British Columbia | CDI College Privacy Policy | Career Training

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we've developed this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used within our sites and services. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.  

When Personal Information Is Collected and How CDI College Uses Your Personal Information

CDI College collects personal information to make our site(s) and service(s) more relevant and rewarding for you to use.

For each visitor to our Web pages, our Web server automatically recognizes your domain, service provider, operating system, and internet browser. Our Web server additionally records usage of pages by our visitors. We use this information, in aggregate, for our research reports and performance surveys. We sometimes use this non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience.

Some of CDI College’s pages request you to provide personally identifiable information in order to participate in the activities and offerings within. We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to our services, to fulfill a request by you, or to contact you about your account with us. Most of our communications provide an "opt-out" feature.

We may also use your information to update internal systems. This allows for seamless delivery of services and resources to you across CDI College.

The CDI College website(s) and service(s) may contain email services, bulletin board services, chat areas, news groups, forums, communities, personal Web pages, calendars, photo displays and/or other message or communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with others (collectively, "Communication Services"). The information we collect in connection with these Communication Services is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these Communication Services. Within many of these Communication Services, CDI College provides you multiple privacy options that allow you to restrict the use and viewability of your information to others.

Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Third party vendors, including Google may use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to CDI College website. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page.

Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Some of our site(s) and service(s) contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy policies as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Will CDI College Disclose My Personal Information To Parties Outside CDI College?

CDI College does not sell, rent, give away, or loan any identifiable information regarding its members to any third party other than agents and contractors of CDI College.

Agents and contractors of CDI College who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for CDI College.

CDI College may release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i.) comply with law, (ii.) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or (iii.) protect the rights, property, or safety of CDI College, our users, or others.

How CDI College Protects Your Information

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, despite all of our efforts, there is always a risk that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions. This reality is true of all Internet use. As a result, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit, and you transmit all information at your own risk.

How You Can Access or Correct Your Information

Many of the online site(s) and service(s) we provide allow you to manage your personal information. Should you need further assistance, please contact us using the contact information provided below.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

How Does CDI College Protect The Privacy Of Children Younger Than 13 Years?

CDI Ccllege is concerned about the privacy of young children and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13 years. We suggest that you become involved with your child's access to the Internet and to our site to ensure that his or her privacy is well protected.

Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your information by CDI College.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If You Have any Questions About This Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the content or practices of our website, you can contact CDI College at: [info@cdicollege.ca](mailto:%20info@cdicollege.ca).
